[Subtitles by danielsangeo]
RRRRRAAAARRRRGH!
[incoherent raging]
Wait!
I have satchel charges!
I can bring this whole building down.
Just need to find the right place.
I need to get higher up,
then I can find some sort of support
beam to really collapse this place.
I forgot I was even holding these things.
Yeah, now I'm feeling a lot better
about how I'm getting out of here.
It's no longer an "if" situation.
Honestly, this amount of
ordnance is a real comfort factor.
It's like having a square
explosive teddy bear.
I need a marker so I can put a
little smiley face on it.
Give it a name.
Now, the most obvious ones are
"Boomer" or "Boo-boo".
But if I named it something like "Chuck",
that has some nice subtleties to it.
Hm, I'm not seeing any
obvious spots here.
It would be better if I could
place the charges
closer to where I could see
daylight at least.
Actually, I could get passed
this conveyor.
I'll try that first, then I'll
blow up the building.
Hah.  Guard rails.
Yeah, safety first!
...'kay...
This isn't so bad...
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
"Radioactive"?!
Are we saying crushing, drowning,
burning, exploding isn't
thorough enough for this place?
Eh, screw it.  I have a Geiger counter
in my suit because I am trendy.
I'm a fashion pioneer.
So, I'll decide for myself if
this place is radioactive or not.
For all I know, they could be
talking about the sun.
It can be seen from a window.
"Warning!"
DROP-OFF!
Ugh!
Are you kidding?  This is even
worse than I expected!
This is something out of cartoon!
Oh my God!
Those jaws killed space bug
like an Earth bug!
Oh, wow!
My lucky day!
This is a dream come true!
I was a kid and I went to
see Santa Claus,
I told him I wanted to be in a cage fight
with these tiny fucking monsters
jumping at my face.
And I wanted the floor to be
made of a giant crusher
that could kill me in one quick motion
AND THE SIDES TO BE SLANTED,
SO IF I SLIPPED, I'D IMMEDIATELY DIE!
AND NOW I HAVE IT ALL!
WHAT MORE COULD I POSSIBLY ASK FOR?!
Christ, I hate having to make
decisions under pressure like this.
Of course, there's only one option, so...
Oh-ho... Jell-O knees...
I feel sore...
I think I'll take a dip in this
thoughtfully provided bath of...
green glowing liquid that's...
Oh, wait, this is a trap.
I'm not falling for that.
This isn't even a spa.
What the fuck?
It's like they're not even trying.
Oh, yeah, "Radiation".
Woo-oo-oo...
Well, my Geiger counter still hasn't
gone off, so, you're a liar, Mr. Sign.
You'll fit right in this place.
What is it with this intense red
lighting and cramped corridors?
I feel like I'm on a sub.
This designer must've been Navy.
Oh, damn.  A grate over top.
Is this necessary?
If there's someone up there,
I'm going to pop up and say I'm
a troll and want some goat meat.
Oh, God, they locked this, too?
All right, well, I don't have
much else to work on.
Oh, that opened right up.
[houndeyes charging up]
Okay, I'm your dance instructor--
NO, YOU'RE STARTING TOO EARLY!
STOP THAT!
I SAID STOP THAT!
1-2-3 LEFT!
NO, NO, YOUR RHYTHM'S ALL WRONG!
Rrrgh!
I give up; I can't teach this class.
Some people just don't
want to learn, y'know?
Oh, hey, there's a box of ammo.
Hell, these will fit the revolver.
I guess being a teacher
does have its perks.
Oh, nice, it comes with a speed-loader.
Though, I guess if you need a speed-loader,
you shouldn't be using a
revolver in the first place.
But, here I am.
In some sort of dog kennel...I guess.
Except I'm on the wrong side of it.
I'm getting out--no, maybe not.
It's the amps that kill you, but
do I really want the volts either?
Well, the people who built this
kennel didn't count on one thing:
I'm not a dog!
Actually, if the fence wasn't electrified,
I think a dog could get out of here.
But, I'm part of the Opposable Thumbs
Club, so I think I'll play it safe.
Oh, yeah, this'll hold me.
Now, the trick here is to NOT do
a belly-flop onto the fence.
That would be worst possible outcome.
Oof!
Oh, boy.
Nothing like the loving embrace
of poured concrete.
Y'know, I'm almost disappointed
I DON'T see anyone following me
because I'd like to see them go
through everything I have.
Or, maybe somebody was following me
but they're dead now because
they tried to keep up.
That would be kind of
flattering in a way.
I'm just that good.
[thumping sound]
What?
WHOA!  How did something THAT
big sneak up on me?
Yeah.
Yeah, that got you to calm down.
I can see you know what this is.
Good.
We're having some
interspecies communication.
Damn, you're as big as a linebacker.
Looks like you have some sort of armor...
An extra appendage...
Yeah, you're definitely more impressive
than the rest of the losers here.
I could see you getting
a job in management.
Well, I'll let somebody else dissect you.
I've already done more than my
share in the name of science today.
[lock jiggles]
What is wrong with this world?
All right, where are the keys?
Do you have them?
No, probably not.
Button's locked...
Computer's locked...
Well, I'm the locksmith!
[alarm sounds]
Alarms?
[crashing sound]
You'd think I would--
OH GOD!
SEE, THIS IS WHY PEOPLE NEED TO
DO THEIR OWN WORK!
WHEN I HAVE TO DO THEIR JOBS FOR
THEM, THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS!
Did I kill it?
WAAAH!
Okay, the bullet test is
inconclusive, so...
Let's see how it responds to a
different set of stimuli.
HYPOTHESIS CONFIRMED!
Christ.
I hate biolabs.
Hey, what's this?
[alarm sounds]
Why did a new set of alarms start?
I don't like this.  I'm leaving.
[lock jiggles]
Why is this door locked?
I didn't even shut this.
[machine powers up]
Shit.
I think this what being an atom feels like.
[electrical explosion]
Oh.
Uh.
Well, I feel okay.
But, something tells me
I might sterile now.
Oh, hey!  I need some help!
Don't be shy!
BLAAAH!
[babbling]
Wow.  That is BEYOND rude.
Oh, shit!
I forgot.
Everyone's trying to kill me.
Yeah.
OF COURSE!
IT'S NOT MY IMAGINATION!
EVERYONE IS TRYING TO KILL ME!
GUARD: Hey, it's no good--
AH HAH!
FOOL ME ONCE, SHAME ON YOU!
FOOL ME TWICE, EVERYONE DIES!
Yeah, I see right through you.
Standing there, acting like
you're my best friend
when you obviously waved that
assassin right on passed you.
I can't trust anyone here.
But, I never did anyway
so I guess there's no problem!
Yoo-hoo!
Over here!
You forgot your bullets!
Take some of mine!
You're welcome!
Hm, I'm going to need some more ammo
if I'm going to kill the whole world.
Oh, here's some guns; that's a start.
I'm a gun farmer.
I plant bullet seeds in people
at about a thousand feet per second and
out pop more guns.
Right now, I'm harvesting.
So.
I admit I really dropped the ball
forgetting everyone was trying to kill me.
That's so unlike me.
Usually, that's the first conclusion
I come to when things go wrong.
If anything, it's less stressful
now since I don't have to wonder
if they're going to kill me.
I know they are.
Oh.  Ammo.
No more second-guessing people
when they give me shifty looks
around the coffee machine or
pass me in the hall.
I can just kill everyone.
It's a catch-all equation.
But, I still don't remember why
everyone's trying to kill me.
I just remember people
showing up and shooting.
That's not very progressive.
[lock buzzes]
Are you kidding me?
This is the fucking lobby!
Why are these doors locked?
From the inside!
P.A.: Access Denied
Who said that?!
Somebody's watching me.
Fine!
They don't want me to leave the
building, I can improvise.
Watch the glass...
I have a good suit but if those
shards got in my eye, oh man.
Dammit.
Come on!
There's no grip.
All right, I'm going to have to
go find a crate or something.
Th-this is doable.
Y'know, I seem to remember
having seen a crate before.
Hm.
Or a grappling hook!
Wow, I could really
use a grappling hook.
I'm going to buy one from Play It Again
Sports or someplace once I get out of here.